Aryan Mehta

am.career11@gmail.com

07446048446

linkedin.com/in/am161

https://aryanmehta.dev/

Summary

Experienced UI/Front-End Development with 2 years of total experience building landing pages and complexed web applications in agile methodologies.

Trained in HTML5, JavaScript ES6+, CSS, TailwindCSS, SCSS, BEM, React, React Router, Redux, React Query, and Axios.

Delivered pixel perfect frontend live applications from Figma designs.

Experience



React Developer

Plume - Learning Technology Agency

Jun 2022 - Dec 2022 (7 months)

- -Developed an e-learning platform estimated to be used by 100,000+
- users as well as a platform for admins to manage the content.
- Used Axios and React Query for state management and REST API calls as well as conditional rendering.
- Created reusable components and custom hooks.
- Responsive and mobile first approach.
- Managed page routes using React Router and slugs.

Javascript Developer

Learn&Co Ltd | Language Agency

Jan 2022 - Jul 2022 (7 months)

- Worked in a team following agile workflow.
- Created reusable components and custom hooks which reduced the code significantly.
- Used Axios for API calls and hooks to manage state.
- Managed page routes using React Router.

Education

The Open University

BSc, Computing, IT and Mathematics 2021 - 2024

Skills

```
css • javascript • figma • git • github • React.js • JSON Web Token (JWT) • Redux.js •
Tailwind CSS · api
```